Guide to the National Law Center records, 1865-2005 RG0014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alumni Relations office, 1884-1989; RG0014 Series 12; 36.5 Linear feet (Box 8, Box 26)
  - 1st, 2nd, law association reunion (1933-34) GWLA scholarship dinner (1941), 1933-1941 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Cherry Tree yearbook, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cherry Tree yearbook, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - NLC dean's report, 1982-1987 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Law alumni photographs, 1921-1989; RG0014 Series 13; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 13, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 15, Box 14, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
  This series contains photographs, biographical sketches, articles and newsletters. The subjects of these photographs include Founder's Day celebrations, Alumni Reunions, Dean Robert Kramer, Dean Jack Friedenthal, Harold Green, Patricia Roberts Harris, Joyce Green, Earl Warren, Oliver Gasch, Warren Burger, Leon Jaworski, John Duncan, Sarah Hughes, Oswald Colclough, Lloyd Elliott, Van Vleck moot court, receptions, Jacob Burns, and buildings.
  - Law Center Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.1)
  - Law Center Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.2)
  - Law Center Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 1.3)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Senior Reception, 03/13/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
    See Print for Identification
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Senior Reception, 03/13/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
    Unidentified
  - Class of 1979 Class Reunion, undated (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.4)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.5)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.6)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.7)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.8)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.9)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.1)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.11)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, Elizabeth Farquhar and Joseph DePaul, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.12)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.13)
    Elizabeth Farquhar and Cong. Michael Barnes
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.14)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.15)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.16)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.17)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.18)
  - G.W. Law Assoc. Mid-Winter Luncheon, 01/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 2.19)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.2)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.21)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.22)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.23)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.24)
  - 116th Founders Day Dinner 1966 Class Reunion, 11/13/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.25)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.26)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.27)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.28)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.29)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.3)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.31)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.32)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.33)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.34)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.35)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.36)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1931, 05/15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2.37)
  - 115th Founders Day Celebration, 11/21/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
    Pres. Lloyd Elliott presents to Chief Justice Mary Stallings
  - Class of 1979 Class Reunion, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.2)
  - Class of 1979 Class Reunion, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.3)
  - Class of 1979 Class Reunion, undated (Box 1, Folder 3.4)
  - 115th Founders Day Celebration, 11/21/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.5)
  - 115th Founders Day Celebration, 11/21/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.6)
  - First Year Law Student Brunch, 08/23/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.7)
  - First Year Law Student Brunch, Dean Jerome Barron and Valerie Perrin, 08/23/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.8)
  - First Year Law Student Brunch, Valerie Perrin and Pres. Lloyd Elliott, 08/23/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.9)
  - First Year Law Student Brunch, 08/23/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.1)
  - First Year Law Student Brunch, 08/23/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.11)
  - National Law Center Commencement, 05/18/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.12)
  - National Law Center Commencement, 05/18/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3.13)
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.5)
    Don Mooers and Hon. Lawrence Margolis
  - Founder's Day, 11/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.6)
    l.to r. ELwood Davis, Glen Wilkinson and Dr. Lloyd Elliott
  - First Year Brunch, 08/20/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.7)
  - First Year Brunch, 08/20/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.8)
  - First Year Brunch, 08/20/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.9)
  - Class of 1934 50th Reunion, 04/13/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.1)
  - Class of 1934 50th Reunion, 04/13/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4.11)
  - List of Founder's Day Photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.12)
    See Document, 2 copies
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.13)
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.14)
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.15)
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.16)
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.17)
  - Founder's Day, 10/29/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.18)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion/Class of 1933, 04/23/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.19)
  - Senior Reception, 03/12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.2)
  - Senior Reception, 03/12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 4.21)
  - Group Photo, undated (Box 1, Folder 4.22)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.23)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.24)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.25)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.26)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.27)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.28)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.29)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.3)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.31)
    Janet Gilbert with Dean Jerome Barron, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.32)
    John W. Jackson with Dean Jerome Barron, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.33)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.34)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.35)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.36)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.37)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.38)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.39)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary/Class of 1932, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.4)
  - Class Reunion/Class of 1975, 03/18/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4.41)
  - GWLAA Annual Mtg., 05/20/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
    Dean Barron receiving silver tray
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 04/20/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Senior Reception Photo List, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Senior Reception, 04/09/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - Senior Reception, 04/09/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.5)
  - Senior Reception, 04/09/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.6)
    See Photo for Identification
  - Senior Reception, 04/09/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.7)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 04/09/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.8)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 03/10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.9)
  - D.C. Alumni Luncheon, 01/28/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.1)
  - D.C. Alumni Luncheon, 01/28/1988 (Box 1, Folder 5.11)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon -Judge Jacob Levin, 05/21/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.12)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon -Judge Jacob Levin, 05/21/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.13)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon (GWLA), 05/21/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.14)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 04/11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.15)
    Myra Barron, Tara Witmer and Dean Jerome Barron
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 04/11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.16)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 04/11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.17)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon/Martin Mendelsohn (speaker), 03/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.18)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon/Martin Mendelsohn, 03/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.19)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon/Martin Mendelsohn, 03/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.2)
  - Commencement, 02/15/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.21)
  - Commencement, 02/15/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.22)
    Dean Jerome Barron (l) and Judge Bruce Mencher
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 02/11/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5.23)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 12/11/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.24)
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 12/11/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.25)
    Jack Olender and guest speaker Dr. J. Clay Smith
  - D.C. Chapter Luncheon, 12/11/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.26)
    (l to r) NLC Student Julie Ford, Cece Ibson with Dr. J. Clay Smith
  - Yong-Kyum Kim and Prof. Mallinson and Prof. Park, 12/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.27)
  - Yong-Kyum Kim and Prof. Mallinson and Prof. Park, 12/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.28)
  - Faculty Alumni Luncheon, 10/23/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.29)
  - Faculty Alumni Luncheon, 10/23/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.3)
  - Senior Reception at National Lawyer's Club, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.31)
  - Senior Reception at National Lawyer's Club, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.32)
    Alan Weinig, Debra Kalmore and Mindy Levine
  - Senior Recepton, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.33)
    Cynthia Psoyas, Mark Schneider, Peter Roberts, Prof. Lewis Schiller
  - Senior Reception, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.34)
    Prof and Mrs. Tom Mallinson and George Indest
  - Senior Reception, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.35)
    Ron Willoner and Kate Garrett
  - Senior Reception, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.36)
    John Jenkins and Franc Perry
  - Senior Reception, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.37)
    Prof. Donald Rothschild, Michael Gaba, Stephen Kozol and Jackie Farino
  - Senior Reception, 03/08/1986 (Box 1, Folder 5.38)
    (l. to r.) Karen Avangliano, Judge James Cacheris, Everett Bellows
  - Founder's Day Dinner Dance, 11/16/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.39)
  - Founder's Day Dinner Dance, 11/16/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.4)
  - Md. State Bar Assoc. Mtg., 06/14/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.41)
    (l.to r.) Asst. Dean John Jenkins, Elizabeth Farquhar, C. Dougherty
  - Md. State Bar Assoc. Mtg., 06/14/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.42)
  - Md. State Bar Assoc. Mtg., 06/14/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.43)
  - Md. State Bar Assoc. Mtg., 06/14/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.44)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1935, 06/07/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.45)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1935, 06/07/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.46)
  - 50 Yr. Reunion Class of 1935, 06/07/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.47)
    3 men posing, Unidentified
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1935, 06/07/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.48)
  - Group Photo, undated (Box 1, Folder 5.49)
  - List of pictures for Senior Reception, 03/30/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.5)
    Unidentified, 2 copies
  - Senior Reception, 03/30/1985 (Box 1, Folder 5.51)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1929, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1929, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1929, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1929, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6.4)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Class of 1929, 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6.5)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.6)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.7)
    Michael Hicks and Dean Robert Kramer
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.8)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.9)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.1)
    Dean Kramer and George Kelser
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.11)
  - First Year Law Student Breakfast, 08/19/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.12)
  - Annual Reception: Md. St. Bar Association, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.13)
  - Annual Commencement of Natl. Law Center, 05/21/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.14)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.15)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.16)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.17)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.18)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.19)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.2)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.21)
  - 50 Yr. Anniversary Reunion Law Class of 1928, 05/05/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.22)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.23)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.24)
    See Photo
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.25)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.26)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.27)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.28)
  - Senior Reception (NLC), 03/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.29)
  - Pres. of Prize Money to Lourdes Mendoza and John Jones in Dean Kramer's Office, 03/22/1978 (Box 1, Folder 6.3)
  - Senior Reception, 03/12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6.31)
  - Senior Reception, 03/12/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6.32)
  - Founder's Day Committee Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.33)
  - Founder's Day Committee Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.34)
  - Founder's Day Committee Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.35)
  - Founder's Day Committee Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 6.36)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/09/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/09/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
    Unidentified, Partial contact sheet
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.4)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.5)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.6)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.7)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.8)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.9)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.1)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.11)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.12)
  - GWLA Senior Reception, 03/15/1980 (Box 1, Folder 7.13)
  - 114th Founder's Day, 11/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.14)
  - 114th Founder's Day, 11/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.15)
  - 114th Founder's Day, 11/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.16)
  - 114th Founder's Day, 11/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.17)
  - 114th Founder's Day, 11/10/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.18)
  - GWLA Mid-Winter Meeting Luncheon in Chicago, 11/02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.19)
  - GWLA Mid-Winter Meeting Luncheon in Chicago, 11/02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.2)
  - GWLA Mid-Winter Meeting Luncheon in Chicago, 11/02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.21)
  - GWLA Mid-Winter Meeting Luncheon in Chicago, 11/02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.22)
  - GWLA Mid-Winter Meeting Luncheon in Chicago, 11/02/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.23)
  - Group Photo, undated (Box 1, Folder 7.24)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.25)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.26)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.27)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.28)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.29)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.3)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.31)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.32)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.33)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.34)
    Prior reception, unidentified
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.35)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion (1929), 05/11/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7.36)
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
    Marvin Center, L. to R. Patrick Grey, Dean Robert Kramer
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
    Dom Di Julia, Fred Daly and Robert Oswald
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.5)
    Philip Herrick, Marion Edwin Harrison
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.6)
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.7)
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.8)
    Patrick Gray III and Marshall Gardner
  - 107th Founder's Day, 11/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.9)
    Marvin Center, Patrick Gray and Pres. Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.1)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.11)
    Pres. Elliott, David Pelton Moore, Brooks Hays
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.12)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.13)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.14)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.15)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.16)
    Bolon Turner and Brooks Hays
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.17)
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.18)
    Patrick Gray/another
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.19)
    Bolon Turner, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.2)
    Lyle Alverson, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.21)
    Brooks Hays and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.22)
    John Larson, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.23)
    H. Cecil Kilpatrick and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.24)
    Sarah Hughes, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.25)
    Samuel L'Hommedieu, Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.26)
    Samuel Roberts and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.27)
    Ross Nichols and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.28)
    Jerome Cox and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.29)
    Ashby E. Bladen and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - 50th Reunion Class of 1922, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.3)
    Janet Dew and Pres. Lloyd Elliott
  - Group Photo, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.31)
  - 106 Founder's Day Luncheon, 10/30/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.32)
    S. Chesterfield Oppenheim, Rae Fichtner
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 8.33)
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.34)
    Judge Oliver Gasch, William T. Fryer
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.35)
    Mrs. Lewis Gable, R. Lewis Gable
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.36)
    David Urey, Oscar Berry and Phillip Herrick
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.37)
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.38)
    Pres. Lloyd Elliott, Al Capp
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.39)
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.4)
    Dallas Shirley, Phillip Herrick and Mrs. Herrick
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.41)
    Judge Oliver Gasch, Newell Ellison, O.C. Coclough
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.42)
    GWU Center, l. to r. Preston Nash '21, Leslie Gaston '40
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.43)
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.44)
    GWU Center, O.S. Coclough '35, Newell Ellison '21
  - 106 Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.45)
    GWU Center, Mrs. Charles Marinaccio, Charles Marinaccio, Judge Oliver Gasch
  - 106th Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.46)
    GWU Center, unidentified
  - 106th Founder's Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 1, Folder 8.47)
  - 105th Anniversary at the Mayflower Hotel, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.1)
    Chairman and Mrs. Morris
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.2)
    Admiral Colclough
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.3)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.4)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.5)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.6)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.7)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.8)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.9)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.1)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.11)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.12)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.13)
  - 105th Anniversary, 10/23/1970 (Box 2, Folder 9.14)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.15)
    Pres. Elliot, John J. Wilson, '21
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.16)
    Pres. Elliot, William I Denning, '13
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.17)
    Pres. Elliot, Josehp E. McCullough, '21
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.18)
    Pres. Elliot, Olivia Geiger Faircloth, '21
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.19)
    David Pelton Moore, Michael Rossman
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.2)
    Pres. Elliot, Andrew Wilkins, '17
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.21)
    Pres. Elliot, Preston M. Nash, '21
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.22)
    Dean Kramer, Joseph E. McCullough, Orville F. Rush, Evertt H. Bellows
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.23)
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.24)
    Miss Mary Ellen Coffey, John J. Wilson, Samuel J. Flickinger
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.25)
    Walter E. Barton, William I. Denning, Joseph C. Fehr, Milan C. Miskovsky
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.27)
    Preston Nash, Joseph C. Fehr, Cato B. Hurd, Walter E. Barton
  - 50th Anniversary Reunion, 05/14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.28)
    Dean Kramer, Pres. Elliot, Preston Nash, Joseph C. Fehr, Cato B. Hurd
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.29)
    L. to R. Judge Oliver Gasch, Newell Ellison, O.C. Coclough
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.3)
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.31)
    L. to R. E.K. Morris, Marshall Gardner, Matthew Clary
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.32)
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.33)
    Henry A. Berliner and Mrs. Berliner
  - 106th Founders Day, 10/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9.34)